Donald C. Stone Papers
Donald C. Stone Papers
1926[?]-1992[?]
Stone, Donald Crawford, 1903-
45 linear ft.
American educator and planner for the Roosevelt and Truman Administrations.
2458927
Scope and Contents of the Collection
Correspondence, conference papers, curricula, articles, diaries, speeches, a few photographs and videotapes.
Related Material
See also the Alan K. Campbell Papers and the records of the Interuniversity Case Program
Subject and Genre Headings
Politics, government and public administration; Campbell, Alan K.; Cleveland, Harlan.; Clinton, Bill, 1946-; Cuomo, Mario M., 1921-2015.; Henry, Laurin L. (Laurin Luther), 1921-; Hiss, Alger.; Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972.; Muskie, Edmund S., 1914-1996.; Stone, Donald Crawford, 1903-; Thornburgh, Dick.; American Consortium for International Public Administration.; Coalition to Improve Management in State and Local Government.; University of Pittsburgh. -- Graduate School of Public and International Affairs.; Government executives, Training of -- United States.; Municipal government -- United States.; Public administration -- Study and teaching -- United States.; State governments.; Correspondence.; Clippings (information artifacts); Curricula.; Diaries.; Photographs.; Proceedings.; Speeches (documents); Videotapes.; Teachers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Background information
  - Biographical information (Box 1)
  - Family correspondence (Box 1)
- Correspondence- Subject Files
  - Afghanistan (Box 1)
  - Africa (Box 1)
  - Alabama (Box 1)
  - Alaska (Box 1)
  - Albuquerque, New Mexico (Box 1)
  - Alcoa Foundation (Box 1)
  - Algeria (Box 1)
  - Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, 1 folder of 3 (Box 1)
  - Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, 2 folders of 3 (Box 2)
  - American Consortium for International Public (Box 2)
  - American Consortium for International Public Administration, 5 folders of 6 (Box 2)
  - American Consortium for International Public Administration, 1 folder of 6 (Box 3)
  - American Management Association (Box 3)
  - American Public Works Association (Box 3)
  - American Society for Public Administration (Box 3)
  - Anaheim, California (Box 3)
  - Ancaster, Ontario (Box 3)
  - Argentina (Box 3)
  - Arizona (Box 3)
  - Arkansas (Box 3)
  - Association of Professional Schools of International Affairs (Box 3)
  - Atlanta, Georgia (Box 4)
  - Australia (Box 4)
  - Austria (Box 4)
  - Babcock - Mary Reynolds Babcock Foundation (Box 4)
  - Baltimore, Maryland (Box 4)
  - Bangladesh (Box 4)
  - Barbados (Box 4)
  - Belgium (Box 4)
  - Belize (Box 4)
  - Bepko, Gerald (Box 4)
  - Blumstein, Alfred (Box 4)
  - Bolivia (Box 4)
  - Botswana (Box 4)
  - Brazil (Box 4)
  - Brookings Institution (Box 4)
  - Bucks County, Pennsylvania (Box 4)
  - Buffalo, New York (Box 4)
  - Buncombe County, North Carolina (Box 4)
  - Burundi (Box 4)
  - California (Box 5)
  - Campbell, Alan K., See United States. Executive Office of the President. Office of Personnel Management
  - Canada (Box 5)
  - Carnegie Mellon University (Box 5)
  - Carnegie Mellon University. Donald C. Stone Symposium on Public Administration, June 13, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Carnegie Mellon University. School of Urban and Public Affairs (Box 5)
  - Carnegie Mellon University. Volkswagen Project (Box 5)
  - Carroll, Michael A. (Box 5)
  - Carrollton - Township of Carrollton, Michigan (Box 5)
  - Carter Administration transition, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Center for Excellence in Government (Box 6)
  - Central America (Box 6)
  - Cities and towns (Box 6)
  - Chairs (Box 6)
  - Chapel Hill, North Carolina (Box 6)
  - Charlotte, North Carolina (Box 6)
  - Chattanooga, Tennessee (Box 6)
  - Chicago, Illinois (Box 6)
  - Chile (Box 6)
  - China (Box 6)
  - Christianity and government (Box 7)
  - Chronicle of Philanthropy (Box 7)
  - Clark County, Nevada (Box 7)
  - Cleveland, Harlan (Box 7)
  - Cleveland, Ohio (Box 7)
  - Clinton, William J. (Box 7)
  - Club of Rome (Box 7)
  - Coalition to Improve Management and Performance in Government (Box 7)
  - Coalition to Improve Management in State and Local Government, 5 folders of 14 (Box 8)
  - Coalition to Improve Management in State and Local Government, 5 folders of 14 (Box 9)
  - Coalition to Improve Management in State and Local Government, 4 folders of 14 (Box 10)
  - Coalition to Improve Management in State and Local Government:
    - City/County Guide (Box 11)
    - Community Affairs Project, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Dispatch #5 (Box 11)
    - Dispatch #6 (Box 11)
    - Dispatch #7 (Box 11)
    - Dispatch #8 (Box 11)
    - Dispatch #9 (Box 11)
    - Dispatch #10 (Box 11)
    - Dispatch #11 (Box 11)
    - Dispatch #12 (Box 11)
    - Guides 1-5 (Box 11)
    - Guide 9 (Box 11)
    - Infoshare 1-5 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 6-10 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 11 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 12 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 13 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 14 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 15 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 16 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 17 (Box 12)
    - Infoshare 19 (Box 12)
  - Cobb County, Georgia (Box 13)
  - Colombia (Box 13)
  - Columbus, Ohio, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Colman, William (Box 13)
  - Colorado (Box 13)
  - Commission on American State and Local Public Service (Box 13)
  - Committee for Economic Development (Box 13)
  - Common Cause (Box 13)
  - Conference on the Public Service (Box 13)
  - Connecticut (Box 14)
  - Contra Costa County, California (Box 14)
  - Cook County, Illinois (Box 14)
  - Cord, Steven (Box 14)
  - Cosmos Club (Box 14)
  - Costa Rica (Box 14)
  - Cuba (Box 14)
  - Cuomo, Mario (Box 14)
  - Cuyahoga County, Ohio (Box 14)
  - Czechoslovakia (Box 14)
  - Dade County, Florida (Box 15)
  - Dane County, Wisconsin (Box 15)
  - Dayton, Ohio (Box 15)
  - Delaware (Box 15)
  - Denmark (Box 15)
  - Denver, Colorado (Box 15)
  - Disarmament (Box 15)
  - Ditchley Foundation (Box 16)
  - Duquesne Light Company (Box 16)
  - Economic Cooperation Administration, See also Marshall Plan (Box 17)
  - Ecuador (Box 17)
  - Egypt (Box 17)
  - Energy and the environment (Box 17)
  - England (Box 17)
  - Episcopal Diocese of Pittsburgh (Box 17)
  - Erie, Pennsylvania (Box 17)
  - Erie County, Pennsylvania (Box 17)
  - Equitable Gas, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (Box 17)
  - Ethics in government (Box 18)
  - Europe (Box 18)
  - European Institute of Public Administration (Box 18)
  - Federal administration (Box 19)
  - Federal administrative management (Box 19)
  - Fiji (Box 19)
  - Florida (Box 19)
  - Forbes, John E. (Box 19)
  - Ford Foundation (Box 19)
  - Foreign assistance (Box 20)
  - Foreign Service Act of 1946 (Box 20)
  - Former students (Box 20)
  - Fort Wayne, Indiana (Box 20)
  - Fort Worth, Texas (Box 20)
  - France (Box 20)
  - Franklin County, Ohio (Box 20)
  - Gardner, John W. (Box 21)
  - Georgia (Box 21)
  - German Marshall Fund of the United States (Box 21)
  - German occupation policy 1946-1950 (Box 21)
  - Germany (Box 21)
  - Ghana (Box 21)
  - Gladieux, Bernard (Box 21)
  - Golden, William T. (Box 21)
  - Government Finance Officers Association (Box 21)
  - Governmental Accounting Standards Board (Box 21)
  - Greece (Box 21)
  - Gruenberg Award (Box 21)
  - Guam (Box 21)
  - Gulick, Luther (Box 21)
  - Guyana (Box 21)
  - Hanover County, Virginia (Box 22)
  - Harry S. Truman Library (Box 22)
  - Harvard University, John F. Kennedy School of Government (Box 22)
  - Hatfield, Massachusetts (Box 22)
  - Hawaii (Box 22)
  - H. J. Heinz Company Foundation (Box 22)
  - Howard Heinz Endowment (Box 22)
  - Henrico County, Virginia (Box 22)
  - Henry, Laurin (Box 22)
  - Hillman, Elsie (Box 22)
  - Hillman Foundation (Box 22)
  - Hillsborough County, Florida (Box 22)
  - Hiss, Alger (Box 22)
  - Hong Kong (Box 22)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, See Uniform Crime Reports
  - Hungary (Box 22)
  - Idaho (Box 23)
  - Illinois (Box 23)
  - Ilchman, Alice Stone (Box 23)
  - Independent sector (Box 23)
  - India, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Indiana, 1 folder of 3 (Box 23)
  - Indiana, 2 folders of 3 (Box 24)
  - Indiana University (Box 24)
  - Indiana University. School of Public and (Box 24)
  - Environmental Affairs (Box 24)
  - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1 folder of 5 (Box 24)
  - Indianapolis, Indiana, 4 folders of 5 (Box 25)
  - Indonesia (Box 25)
  - Institute of Public Administration (Box 25)
  - Inter-American Public Works Conference, San Juan, Puerto Rico, March, 1972 (Box 25)
  - Intergovernmental cooperation (Box 25)
  - Intergovernmental Personnel Act of 1969 (Box 26)
  - Intergovernmental policy (Box 26)
  - International Association of Chiefs of Police (Box 26)
  - International Association of Schools and (Box 26)
  - Institutes of Administration, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - International City Management Association, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - International Conference on Improving Public Management and Performance, Washington, DC, 1979 (Box 26)
  - International Institute of Administrative Sciences, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - International Labour Office (Box 26)
  - International Partnership Initiative, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - International Partnership Initiatives Congress, Wolfsburg, Germany, SSep 1990 (Box 27)
  - International Union of Local Authorities (Box 27)
  - Iowa (Box 27)
  - Iran, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Iraq (Box 27)
  - Ireland (Box 28)
  - Isabella County, Michigan (Box 28)
  - Israel (Box 28)
  - Italy (Box 28)
  - J, 1 folder (Box 28)
  - Jamaica (Box 28)
  - Japan, 3 folders (Box 28)
  - Japanese-United States cooperation (Box 28)
  - Johnson County, Kansas (Box 28)
  - Jones, Roger W. (Box 28)
  - Jordan (Box 28)
  - K, 1 folder (Box 29)
  - Kansas (Box 29)
  - Kauai County, Hawaii (Box 29)
  - Kenosha County, Wisconsin, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Kent County, Delaware (Box 29)
  - Kentucky (Box 29)
  - Kenya (Box 29)
  - King County, Washington (Box 29)
  - Ethel and Philip Klutznik Charitable Trusts (Box 29)
  - Kolderie, Ted (Box 29)
  - Korb, Lawrence (Box 29)
  - Korea (Box 29)
  - Korten, David C. (Box 30)
  - Kuwait (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - L, 1 folder (Box 30)
  - Laingen, L. Bruce (Box 30)
  - Laurel Foundation (Box 30)
  - Lebanon (Box 30)
  - Leland County, Michigan (Box 30)
  - Lesotho (Box 30)
  - Liberated areas administration (Box 30)
  - Liberia (Box 30)
  - Likert, Rensis (Box 31)
  - Lilly Endowment, Inc. (Box 31)
  - Local Government Academy (Box 31)
  - Los Angeles County, California (Box 31)
  - Louisiana (Box 31)
  - Lucas County, Ohio (Box 31)
  - Lybia (Box 31)
  - MacArthur - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation (Box 31)
  - Madagascar (Box 31)
  - Maine (Box 31)
  - Majewski, Virginia (Box 31)
  - Malaysia (Box 31)
  - Manitowoc County, Wisconsin (Box 31)
  - Marshall Plan, 2 folders (Box 32)
    See also Economic Cooperation Administration
  - Maryland (Box 32)
  - Massachusetts (Box 32)
  - Mauritania (Box 32)
  - Mellon Bank Foundation (Box 32)
  - Richard King Mellon Foundation (Box 32)
  - Mecklenberg County, North Carolina (Box 32)
  - Mexico (Box 33)
  - Michigan, 3 folders (Box 33)
  - Miles, Michael (Box 33)
  - Minnesota, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Mississippi (Box 33)
  - Missouri (Box 33)
  - Jean Monnet Council (Box 33)
  - Montana (Box 33)
  - Montgomery County, Ohio (Box 33)
  - Morocco (Box 33)
  - Muskie, Edmund S. (Box 33)
    See also Intergovernmental Personnel Act of 1969
  - N, 1 folder (Box 34)
  - National Academy of Public Administration: District of Columbia statehood (Box 34)
  - Nominations (Box 34)
  - Office of Federal Management Project (Box 34)
  - Presidency Project (Box 34)
  - Presidency Report 1980 (Box 34)
  - Renewing Our Capacity for Governance Conference 1992 (Box 34)
  - Reports (Box 34)
  - National Assistance Management Association (Box 34)
  - National Association of Counties (Box 35)
  - National Association of Schools of Public Affairs and Administration (Box 35)
  - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers (Box 35)
  - National Association of State Budget Officers (Box 35)
  - National Association of State Personnel Executives (Box 35)
  - National Association of State Training and Development Directors (Box 35)
  - National Association of Towns and Townships (Box 35)
  - National defense - administrative management work (Box 35)
  - National defense reorganization (Box 35)
  - National Institute of Public Affairs (Box 35)
  - National Council of Churches (Box 35)
  - Nebraska (Box 35)
  - Nepal (Box 35)
  - Netherlands (Box 35)
  - Nevada (Box 36)
  - New Hampshire (Box 36)
  - New Jersey (Box 36)
  - New Mexico (Box 36)
  - New York, 4 folders of 5 (Box 36)
  - New York, 1 folder of 5 (Box 37)
  - New Zealand (Box 37)
  - Nigeria, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Nord Family Foundation (Box 37)
  - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) (Box 37)
  - North Carolina (Box 37)
  - North Dakota (Box 37)
  - Ohio (Box 37)
  - Oklahoma (Box 37)
  - Oregon (Box 38)
  - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (Box 38)
  - Ottawa County, Michigan (Box 38)
  - PPG Industries Foundation (Box 38)
  - Pakistan (Box 38)
  - Pan American Union, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Papua New Guinea (Box 38)
  - Paraguay (Box 38)
  - Partners for Livable Places (Box 38)
  - Pecora, Frank A. (Box 38)
  - Peoria, Illinois (Box 38)
  - Peoria County, Illinois (Box 38)
  - Pennsylvania (Box 38)
  - Peru (Box 38)
  - Philippines (Box 38)
  - Phoenix, Arizona (Box 39)
  - Pima County, Arizona (Box 39)
  - Pitt-Carnegie Center for Planning and Urban Development (Box 39)
  - Pittsburgh Foundation (Box 39)
  - Pittsburgh National Bank Foundation (Box 39)
  - Pittsburgh, University of, See University of Pittsburgh
  - Poland (Box 39)
  - Policy Studies Organization (Box 39)
  - Portugal (Box 39)
  - Public administration education (Box 39)
  - Public Administration Review (Box 39)
  - Public Administration Service, 5 folders (Box 40)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 40)
  - Qatar (Box 40)
  - Reagan Administration (Box 40)
  - Remaking Cities Conference, Pittsburgh (Box 40)
  - Pennsylvania, Mar 1988 (Box 40)
  - Report writing technique (Box 41)
  - Returned Peace Corps Volunteers Conference, Mar 1965 (Box 41)
  - Rhode Island (Box 41)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 41)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (Box 41)
  - Rosentraub, Mark (Box 41)
  - Royal Institute of Public Administration (Box 41)
  - Rwanda (Box 41)
  - Saudi Arabia (s), 2 folder (Box 41)
  - Schaetzel, J. Robert (Box 41)
  - Schenectady County, New York (Box 41)
  - Scott, Hugh, See Intergovernmental Personnel Act of 1969
  - Senegal (Box 41)
  - Sierra Leone (Box 41)
  - Singapore (Box 42)
  - Soros Foundation (Box 42)
  - South Africa, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - South Carolina (Box 42)
  - South Dakota (Box 42)
  - Spain (Box 42)
  - Springfield College (Box 42)
  - Sri Lanka (Box 42)
  - Staats, Elmer (Box 42)
  - State management programs (Box 42)
  - State governments
    - Gubernatorial powers (Box 42)
    - Location of executive functions (Box 42)
  - State municipal leagues (Box 42)
  - Stein, Sydney (Box 42)
  - Stevenson, Adlai (Box 42)
  - Stone, Harold A. (Box 42)
  - Sudan, 1 folder of 2 (Box 42)
  - Sudan, 1 folder of 2 (Box 43)
  - Surinam (Box 43)
  - Sweden (Box 43)
  - Swaziland (Box 43)
  - Switzerland (Box 43)
  - Syracuse University (Box 43)
  - Syracuse University. Maxwell School of Citizenship and Public Affairs (Box 43)
  - Taiwan (Box 43)
  - Tanganyika (Box 43)
  - Tangiers (Box 43)
  - Tanzania (Box 43)
  - Tennessee (Box 43)
  - Texas (Box 43)
  - Thailand (Box 43)
  - Thornburgh, Richard (Box 43)
  - Total quality management (Box 43)
  - Tunisia (Box 44)
  - Turkey (Box 44)
  - Uganda (Box 44)
  - UNESCO Preparatory Commission (Box 44)
  - Uniform Crime Reports (Box 44)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (Box 44)
  - United Arab Emirates (Box 44)
  - United Nations (Box 44)
  - United Nations Association (Box 44)
  - United Nations Development Program (Box 44)
  - United Nations Preparatory Commission (Box 44)
  - United States. Agency for International Development (Box 45)
  - United States. Atomic Energy Commission (Box 45)
  - United States. Bureau of the Budget, See United States. Executive Office of the President. Bureau of the Budget
  - United States. Civil Works Administration (Box 45)
  - United States. Department of State (Box 45)
  - United States. Economic Cooperation Administration (Box 45)
  - United States. Executive Office of the President. Bureau of the Budget
    - General, 6 folders of 13 (Box 45)
    - General, 7 folders of 13 (Box 46)
    - Administrative Management Division (4 folders) (Box 47)
    - Daily Intelligence (Box 47)
    - Drafting Replies to White House Correspondence (Box 47)
    - Government reorganization (Box 47)
  - United States. Executive Office of the President. Office of Management and Budget, 2 folders (Box 48)
  - United States. Mutual Security Agency (Box 48)
  - United States. Office of Management and Budget, See United States. Executive Office of the President. Office of Management and Budget
  - United States. Office of Personnel Management (Box 48)
  - University administration, 4 folders of 7 (Box 49)
  - University administration, 3 folders of 7 (Box 50)
  - University of Denver (Box 50)
  - University of Georgia (Box 50)
  - University of Pittsburgh. Graduate School of Public and International Affairs
    - General, 3 folders of 37 (Box 51)
    - General, 4 folders of 37 (Box 52)
    - General, 4 folders of 37 (Box 52)
    - General, 4 folders of 37 (Box 53)
    - General, 4 folders of 37 (Box 54)
    - General, 10 folders of 37 (Box 55)
    - General, 5 folders of 37 (Box 56)
    - General, 3 folders of 37 (Box 57)
    - General, 4 folders of 37 (Box 58)
    - Bulletins (Box 59)
    - Development (Box 59)
    - Faculty recruitment (Box 59)
    - History, 2 folders of 14 (Box 59)
    - History, 4 folders of 14 (Box 60)
    - History, 5 folders of 14 (Box 61)
    - History, 3 folders of 14 (Box 62)
    - Manual of Operations (Box 62)
    - Donald and Alice Stone Fund (Box 62)
    - Ten Year Plans, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Urban Institute (Box 63)
  - Uruguay (Box 63)
  - Utah (Box 63)
  - Venezuela (Box 63)
  - Vermont (Box 63)
  - Vietnam (Box 63)
  - Virginia (Box 63)
  - Volcker Commission (Box 63)
  - War and peace (Box 64)
  - Washington (Box 64)
  - Wells, Herman B. (Box 64)
  - West Virginia (Box 64)
  - Westinghouse Foundation (Box 64)
  - Wisconsin (Box 64)
  - Women, 1 folder of 2 (Box 64)
  - Women, 1 folder of 2 (Box 65)
  - World Bank (Box 65)
  - World Health Organization (Box 65)
  - Writing - composition (Box 65)
  - Wyoming, 4 folders (Box 65)
  - X, Y, Z, 1 folder (Box 66)
  - Yugoslavia (Box 66)
  - Zaire (Box 66)
  - Zambia (Box 66)
  - Zimbabwe (Box 66)
- Writings
  - Articles
    - Lists of publications (Box 67)
    - 1929-1935, 3 folders (Box 67)
    - 1938-1958, 3 folders (Box 68)
    - 1963-1990, undated, 5 folders (Box 69)
  - Books
    - Chicago Police Problems, 1931 (Box 70)
    - Educating the Innovative Public Manager, 1939 (Box 70)
    - The Management of Municipal Public Works, 1981 (Box 70)
  - Conference papers
    - Various, 1939-1965; 4 folders (Box 71)
    - Various, 1966-1990; undated; 5 folders (Box 72)
  - Curricula
    - American University (Box 73)
    - Carnegie Mellon University
      - Administration and Management in Developing Countries, 4 folders (Box 73)
      - Advanced Administrative Management, 4 folders of 7 (Box 74)
      - Advanced Administrative Management, 3 folders of 7 (Box 75)
      - Applied Administrative Management in the Federal System (Box 75)
      - Executive Program (Box 75)
      - Intergovernmental Systems (Box 76)
      - Master of Public Management Program, 5 folders (Box 76)
    - Coalition to Improve Management in State and Local Government, 2 folders (Box 77)
    - Industrial College of the Armed Forces (Box 77)
    - National Academy of Public Administration: Intergovernmental Policy and Program Management, 4 folders of 5 (Box 77)
    - National Academy of Public Administration: Intergovernmantal Policy and Program Management, 1 folders of 5 (Box 78)
    - New York State Public Service Training Program
      - Administration, Course I (Box 78)
      - Administration, Course II (Box 78)
      - Administration, Course III (Box 78)
      - Administration, Course IV, 2 folders (Box 78)
      - Supervision, Course I, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Supervision, Course II, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Supervision, Course III, 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Supervision, Course IV, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Syracuse University (Box 79)
    - United States. Executive Office of the President. Bureau of the Budget (Box 79)
    - University of Pittsburgh
      - Administrative Theory and Process (Box 80)
      - Applied Administrative Management, 2 folders (Box 80)
      - Budgeting (Box 80)
      - Comparative University Administration, 3 folders of 6 (Box 80)
      - Comparative University Administration, 3 folders of 6 (Box 81)
      - Executive Management, 3 folders of 6 (Box 81)
      - Planning and Implementation in Developing Nations (Box 82)
      - Public Works and Developing Countries, 3 folders (Box 82)
      - Teaching hints (Box 82)
      - Urban Program Development and Executive Management, 3 folders (Box 83)
      - Westinghouse Cross-cultural Operations Workshop (Box 83)
  - Diaries, 1939-1982; 8 folders (Box 84)
  - Interviews (Box 84)
  - Letters to editors, 1975-1991 (Box 84)
  - Reports
    - Reports, 1926-1940; 4 folders (Box 85)
    - Reports, 1942-1964; 4 folders (Box 86)
    - Reports, 1970-1980, undated; 5 folders (Box 87)
  - Speeches
    - List of speeches (Box 88)
    - Speeches, 1929-1946; 16 folders (Box 88)
    - Speeches, 1947-1958; 12 folders (Box 89)
    - Speeches, 1959-1968; 10 folders (Box 90)
    - Speeches, 1969-1992, undated; 10 folders (Box 91)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Miscellaneous, 1926-1937; 5 folders (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous, 1938-1969; 4 folders (Box 93)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1992, undated; 4 folders (Box 94)
      See also Memorabilia: Computer diskettes
- Memorabilia
  - Appointment books, 1958-1973 (Box 95)
  - Awards
    - Maxwell Public Service Award, Jun 1967 (Box 95)
    - United States. General Accounting Office, Public Service Award, Nov 1980 (Box 95)
  - Clippings (Box 96)
  - Computer diskettes (Box 96)
  - Diploma: Master of Science in Public Administration, Syracuse University, Jun 1926 (Box 96)
  - Photographs (Box 96)
  - Videotapes (11) (Box 96)